weeklyplus.com 2012-12-17

# WeeklyPlus.com Privacy Policy

_Last updated March 3, 2011_

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the WeeklyPlus.com website. WeeklyPlus, LLC, a Colorado company, the provider of the Website (referred to as "us" or "we"), is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the "User" or the "End User") and how we use that information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us.

### PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.

WeeklyPlus, LLC has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at 110 16th St. Suite 406, Denver, CO 80202 If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site.

The Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live, and we're starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts, buy goods and services, and communicate with others from around the world. It's important to WeeklyPlus.com to help our customers retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer.

We believe your business is nobody else's. Your privacy is important to you and to us. So we'll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, WeeklyPlus.com follows different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

  * We won't sell or distribute your name, mailing address, phone number, email address or any other information to anyone.
  * We'll use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users.

### NOTICE

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requests when you create an account on the Site or when you buy-in to an awesome deal, sign up for our newsletter or join a limited-access portion of the Site. We use Personal Information for four primary purposes:

  * To make the Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * To help you quickly find software, services or information.
  * To help us create content most relevant to you.
  * To alert you to Deals-of-the-Week, special offers, updated information and other new services from WeeklyPlus.com.

### 1\. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the "Privacy Policy" section of the Website. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the Website. It is the responsibility of each User to review the Website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. If we change how we use your personally identifiable information, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### 2\. CONSENT

If you choose not to register or provide Personal Information, you can still use most of WeeklyPlus.com. But you will not be able to access areas that require registration, such as buying in to great Deals in your city.

If you decide to register, you will be able to select the kinds of information you want to receive from us by subscribing to various services, like our electronic newsletters. If you do not want us to communicate with you about other offers regarding WeeklyPlus.com products, programs, events, or services by email, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from WeeklyPlus.com.

### 3\. USER CHOICES ON COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION

As a condition of purchase of our products and services, we require your permission to send you Administrative and Promotional emails. We will send you information regarding your account activity and purchases as well as updates about our products and promotional offers. You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. "Administrative Emails" relate to a User's activity on the Website, and include emails regarding a particular User's account, requests or inquiries, and purchases of products and services. In contrast to Administrative Emails, however, you do have a choice with respect to Promotional Emails. Promotional Emails advertise our products and services, including exclusive sales and other offers, and/or the products and services of our Advertisers and Affiliates. We send Promotional Emails to Users who register with us and have not opted-out of receiving Promotional Emails. If you do not want to receive Promotional Emails from us, you may elect to opt-out of receiving Promotional Emails at any time after registering by e-mailing us at service@weeklyplus.com, by writing to us at the address contained herein, or by hitting the "unsubscribe" button at the bottom of any of our e-mails. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Promotional Emails you do not want to receive.

### 4\. ACCESS

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your Personal Information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time in the member area of WeeklyPlus.com. There you can:

  * View and edit Personal Information you have already given us.
  * Tell us whether you want us to send you marketing information through the 'Update your email preferences' at the bottom of each Promotional Email.
  * Sign up for electronic newsletters about WeeklyPlus.com products and services through the 'Update your email preferences' at the bottom of each Promotional Email.
  * Register. Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on WeeklyPlus.com, your information stays with you.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at service@weeklyplus.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### 5\. SECURITY

WeeklyPlus.com has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

In addition, your transactions are guaranteed under the Fair Credit Billing Act. This Act states that your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 in fraudulent credit card charges. If your bank does hold you liable for $50.00 or les, we'll cover your liability provided the unauthorized, fraudulent use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own and from purchases made from us over our secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

WeeklyPlus.com strictly protects the security of your Personal Information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States of America or any other country where WeeklyPlus.com, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your user name and password, so do not share these with others.

### 6\. NOTICE TO PARENTS

Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children's privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.

The WeeklyPlus.com Site does not publish content that is targeted to children.

### 7\. ENFORCEMENT

If for some reason you believe WeeklyPlus.com has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by email at service@weeklyplus.com, and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

### 8\. DATA TRACKING

**Cookies.** To facilitate and customize your experience with the Website, we store cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small pageText file that is stored on a User's computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use cookies to save you time while using the Website, remind us who you are, and track and target User interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on. Use of this information helps us to create a more user-friendly experience for all visitors. In addition, we may use Third Party Advertising Companies to display advertisements on our Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, some parts of the Website may not work properly.

**Other Tracking Devices.** We use other industry standard technologies like pixel tags and web beacons to track your use of our Website pages and promotions, and allow our Third Party Service Providers to use these devices on our behalf. Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certain pages on our Website, or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. When you access these pages or open or click an email, pixel tags and web beacons generate a Non-Personally Identifiable notice of that action. Pixel tags allow us to measure and improve our understanding of visitor traffic and behavior on our Website, as well as give us a way to measure our promotions and performance. We may also utilize pixel tags and web beacons provided by our Affiliates and/or Marketing Partners for the same purposes.

### 9\. WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE

When you join WeeklyPlus.com, you provide us with your contact information, including your full name and email address. We use this information to send you updates about your order, service and announcements about new and exciting services that we offer. When you order from us, we ask for your credit card number and billing address. We use this information in case you want to order from us again, but we do not use this information again without your permission.

**We may share your information with Authorized Third Party Service Providers.** We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, process payments, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

**We may share your information in a Business Transfer.** As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personally Identifiable Information. However, Personally Identifiable Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

**We may share your information for our Protection and the Protection of Others.** WeeklyPlus.com will disclose your Personal Information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on WeeklyPlus.com or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of WeeklyPlus.com and its family or Websites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of WeeklyPlus.com, its Websites, or the public.

### 10\. MISCELLANEOUS PRIVACY ISSUES

**Children.** Minors under the age of 13 may not use the Website. We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known to be under the age of 13, and no part of the Website is designed to attract anyone under the age of 13.

**Public Areas.** We may provide areas on our Website where you can publicly post information about yourself, can communicate with others, or can review products, restaurants, and submit media content. This information may be accessible by other consumers and companies and may appear on other websites or web searches, and therefore this information could be read, collected, and used by others. For example, if you post your email address along with a public restaurant review, you may receive unsolicited messages. We have no control over who reads your postings or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any personal information.

**Refer A Friend.** If you choose to use our referral service to email a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. WeeklyPlus.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of your referral.

Your friend may contact us at service@weeklyplus.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Facebook Connect.** You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**Links to Third Party Sites.** If you click on a link to a third party site, you will leave the weeklyplus.com site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as [name of company/URL]. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to an [name of company/URL] site, you should read that site's privacy statement before providing any personally identifiable information.

**Testimonials.** We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. We also post publicly available reviews from other sites. If you wish to request your testimonial or review to be removed please contact us at service@weeklyplus.com.

**Notice of Privacy Rights to California Residents.** California law requires that we provide you with a summary of your privacy rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (the "Act") and the California Business and Professions Code. As required by the Act, we will provide you with the categories of Personally Identifiable Information that we collect through the Website and the categories of third party persons or entities with whom such Personally Identifiable Information may be shared for direct marketing purposes at your request. California law requires us to inform you, at your request, (1) the categories of Personally Identifiable Information we collect and what third parties we share that information with; (2) the names and addresses of those third parties; and (3) examples of the products marketed by those companies. The Act further requires us to allow you to control who you do not want us to share that information with. To obtain this information, please send a request by email or standard mail to the address found below. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Personally Identifiable Information you do not want us to share with Affiliated Businesses or Marketing Partners. The request should be sent to the attention of our legal department, and labeled "California Customer Choice Notice." Please allow 30 days for a response. Also, please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information or requesting this notice.

### 11\. CONTACT US

**Corporate Address**  
WeeklyPlus, LLC  
110 16th St. Suite 406  
Denver, CO 80202  
800-520-6920

**For Customers**  
Please use the "[Contact](http://www.weeklyplus.com/contact/)" link here or from our web site for Customer Service Inquiries
